{"data":[{"question":"The women would spend their time to make bread and bullets for the soldiers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would","b":"their","c":"to make","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To make-> making","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The women were indignant and decided that they themselves would do one more effort to drive off the enemy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"decided","c":"do","d":"to drive","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Do-> make","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The delay to prevent the surrender and allowed time for reinforcements to arrive and drive off the enemy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to prevent","b":"allowed","c":"to arrive","d":"drive","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To prevent-> prevented","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The Japanese first developed fake food in the 1920s to introduce people to unfamiliar West dishes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Japanese","b":"developed","c":"in","d":"West","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- West-> western","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"David was a young man who working in an office in a big city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"who","c":"working","d":"an","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Working-> worked","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"He decided to have a holiday in a beautiful place in the mountains where there were much streams.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to have","b":"in","c":"where","d":"much","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Much-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"A rich men and his wife went in a shop to buy a bracelet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"men","b":"wife","c":"in","d":"to buy","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Men->man","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"She traveled to villages and religious centers, with only an interpreter and a few men to carry her camping equipments.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"traveled","b":"religious","c":"men","d":"equipments","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Equipments-> equipment","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"She adopted a fifteen-years-old Sikkimese boy to travel with her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"adopted","b":"fifteen-years-old","c":"to travel","d":"with","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Fifteen-years-old-> fifteen-year-old","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"One day a lady saw a mouse to run across her kitchen floor.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"One","b":"saw","c":"to run","d":"kitchen","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To run-> running","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}